# Bill Ang Li

Computer Science student at University of Toronto

libill12@hotmail.com

## Summary

I am a Computer Science student at the University of Toronto with more than 3 years of programming experience including Java and Python. I have built several winning projects at hackathons as a team member. I am a passionate problem-solver who is keen to take on new challenges.

## Experience

#### Camp Counsellor

June 2017 - September 2017 (4 months)

Led various survival camp activities for children from underprivileged areas of Toronto. Supervised all campers overnight.

#### **Basketball Coach**

November 2015 - June 2016 (8 months)

Led and trained players of ages 5-15 during games and practice.

## Education

University of Toronto

Bachelor of Science - BS, Specialist in Computer Science, Major in Economics, 2017 - 2021 Richmond Hill High School

2013 - 2017

### Honors and Awards

Valedictorian of the Class of 2017

# Bill Ang Li

Computer Science student at University of Toronto

libill12@hotmail.com



Contact Bill Ang on LinkedIn